

# Full Stack Software Engineer

badinescumariuscatalin@yahoo.com 0684435153

Tilburg, Netherlands

# Catalin - Marius Badinescu

### **Profile**

I'm a Full Stack Developer living in Tilburg with over 2 years of experience in building and maintaining web applications.

I love the web but even more than that, I love bringing ideas and designs to life.

I'm passionate about my work, I am transparent, easy to communicate with, have a keen eye on UI/UX, I am easy to talk to, and always seeking to create bridges between technical and non-technical people.

### **Education**

ICT & Software Engineering, Fontys University of Applied Sciences, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

08/2017-06/2021

# **Key Experiences**

#### Full Stack Developer at Bizcuit, Utrecht

03/2022—Present

- Worked on the legacy system as a full stack developer where I had to maintain and release new features for the existing product working with Node.JS, React.JS, PostgreSQL
- Worked on the new system releasing features working with GraphQL (Apollo), SST Framework, Node.JS, Typescript, React.JS and DynamoDB
- Doing various tasks related to cloud services like using AWS
   Cloudwatch for debugging, and creating alarms and dashboards
- Always in contact with all the major banks in the Netherlands in order to solve issues with our product but also provide support for their own issues that we encountered

#### Full Stack Developer at Accenture, Heerlen

10/2021-02/2022

- Worked on a dashboard in React.JS for one of the biggest banks in Germany (Deutsche Bank)
- Assisted the back-end team in creating APIs that would fit UI/UX needs
- Assisted DevOps team in creating a pipeline that would fit both Accenture and the client environment

### Links

<u>Linkedin</u>
<u>CV ( short & full version )</u>

#### Courses

Python Course at InfoAcademy 02/2016—04/2016

AWS Technical Essentials 04/2023-04/2023

### **Skills**

Node.JS / Deno	4/5
React.JS / Next.JS	4/5
Vue.JS / Nuxt.JS	4/5
JavaScript	4/5
PostgreSQL / MySQL	4/5
C# / .NET	3/5
AWS	
Python	2/5
DynamoDB	2/5
MongoDB	
Microsoft Azure	2/5

# Languages

English	Highly proficient
Romanian	Native speaker

#### Full Stack Developer at Wolfpack, Eindhoven

#### 07/2021-09/2021

- Maintaining and adding features to my project during my graduation internship project.
- Released a custom PDF reports exporter
- Released an MVP of an education platform
- Helped maintain multiple projects in the company

# Graduation Internship at Wolfpack, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

#### 01/2021-06/2021

- Created a small Nest.JS back-end application used to upload content for ads campaigns to Azure Blob Storage and to Salesforce using SOQL queries
- A Nuxt.JS front-end application that would allow the client to see orders and upload ads for certain media campaigns
- Deployment initially on Heroku for proof on concept and then to production using Azure DevOps
- Created Apex triggers and functions in Salesforce that will allow to communicate with the Nest.JS back-end application

# Front-end Web Developer at Wolfpack, Eindhoven (Netherlands)

09/2020-01/2021

Created a dashboard (using Nuxt.JS / Vue.JS) where multiple nursing homes in the Netherlands could be managed by their employees.

## **Internships**

#### Front-end web developer at Accenture, Utretch

09/2019-08/2020

I had a 6 month school internship + 6 month extension working for a client (Shell)

- Created a web application for internal use in React.JS
- Researched and deployed a BI tool instance that could be connected to a custom external system to create various dashboards
- Create a back-end application in Node.JS that could get daily data from different systems (like SonarQube, Jira etc.) in order to use it to create various dashboards